experience

UX Design Intern

June 2017 - September 2017

Gain Life

Currently developing multiple features of an iOS app for a start-up company.

Graphic Designer

May 2016 - May 2017

Enactus SFU

I was in charge of the entire design direction of the Bright Ideas program, including work such as changing the branding direction, redesigning the website, and collaborating with the Marketing Manager.

volunteer

Mentor

Seattle Design Charrette

Guided students in a weekend long design charrette held in Seattle for a second year spatial design course at SFU.

awards

Enactus Canada Regional Champion

March 2017

March 2017

Designed the presentation slide deck for the The winning team of Scotiabank Youth Empowerment Challenge Regional Champion for Enactus Canada Regional Exposition.

Seattle Design Charrette

March 2016

1st out of 17 teams in a weekend long spatial design charrette held in Seattle.

Canon Canada Photography Award

May 2015

First place in a Digital Photography course in the School of Interactive
Arts and Technology program at Simon Fraser University.

link: https://flic.kr/s/aHskb913Dg

education

Simon Fraser University

2014 - present

Interactive Arts & Technology, B.A. Design Concentration

language

Fluent in both English and Japanese

kosuke futsukaichi

(604) 339 2981

thekosuke929@gmail.com

thekosuke.com

about

I was born in Japan, made in Arizona and currently learning in Vancouver. I stay current on hip hop and basketball, and I enjoy watching interviews. I hope my contribution to the process in the field of design will impact real life experiences.

skills

Design Technical Strategy Sketch

User Experience Flinto

User Interface Invision

Interaction Design Photoshop

Visual Design

Illustrator